Guide to the Richard W. Lyman Personal Papers SC0562
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2014-099
  - Research and Writing
    - U.S. Politics, 1991-1992 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Politics, 1992-1994 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Politics, 1988-2000 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Politics, 1996 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Stanford in Turmoil Research (1/2), 2009 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Stanford in Turmoil Research (2/2), 2009-2010 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Politics, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Politics, 1996 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1996, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Award - Marquis Who's Who Publications Board, 2010 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Research - Bibliographic, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Speech Materials, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Reprints for Research, 1982-2000 (Box 77)
  - Boards/Committees
    - World Affairs Council, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Independent Sector - Scrapbook, 1986-1990 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Chase Manhattan - Board Members, 1989-1991 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Chase - Drysdale, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - RWL to Board, 1981-1991 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Chase, 1989-1991 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - National Bank Director's Book, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Lexia - Current, 1994-1996 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Lexia - Board, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Lexia Settlement, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Lexia, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Lexia: Chron. File, 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Lexia Meeting, 1996 July (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - IBM Files, 1979-1991 (Box 78)
      Access to Collection
      The materials are closed for 75 years from date of creation.
  - Photographs
    - Photographs of RW Lyman and the Advisory Council of the Institute for International Studies, circa 1991 (Box 78)